Finding Aid for the Republic Pictures Corporation Records LSC.0979
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Shooting Scripts
  - Is There a Duchess in the House? [1977].; sw: Jack Townley, Lillie Hayward; series: Deluxe., 1954 (Box 77, 81, 82, 96)
  - It Might Happen to You [633]., 1937. (Box 89)
  - Jaguar [1993].; sw: John Fenton Murray & Benedict Freedman; series: Deluxe., 1955 (Box 130)
  - Jamboree [1252]., 1943. (Box 111)
  - Jesse James at Bay [1121].; series: Roy Rogers., 1941 (Box 67)
  - Jim Hanvey, Detective [638]., 1937. (Box 76)
  - Joan of Ozark [1090]., 1942. (Box 67)
  - Johnny Doughboy [1160]., 1942. (Box 91)
  - Join the Marines [635]., 1937. (Box 106)
  - Jubilee Trail [1945].; sw: Bruce Manning; series: Deluxe., 1953 (Box 99)
  - Jungle Drums of Africa [1935].; sw: Ronald Davidson., 1952 (Box 87)
  - Juvenile Jungle [6090].; sw: Arthur T. Horman., 1957 (Box 35)
  - Kansas Terrors [914].; series: Mesquiteer., 1939 (Box 73)
  - King of the Cowboys [1204]., 1942. (Box 115)
  - King of the Gamblers [1670].; sw: Albert DeMond and Bradbury Foote; series: Variety., 1947 (Box 123)
  - King of the Newsboys [786]., 1938. (Box 128)
  - Lady from Louisiana [958].; sw: Vera Gaspery., 1940 (Box 70)
  - The Lady Wants Mink [1948].; sw: Dane Lussier and Richard Allan Simmons; series: Deluxe., 1952 (Box 94, 129)
  - Lake Placid Serenade [1247].; sw: Dick Irving Highland, Doris Gilbert., 1944 (Box 117)
  - Laramie Trail [1406]., 1943. (Box 118)
  - Larceny on the Air [671]., 1937. (Box 75)
  - The Last Crooked Mile [1475].; sw: Jerry Sackheim; series: Anniversary., 1945 (Box 110)
  - The Last Frontier Uprising [1588].; sw: Harvey H. Gates; series: All Star., 1946 (Box 122)
  - The Last Musketeer [1810].; sw: Arthur Orloff; series: Paramount., 1951 (Box 108)
  - Last of the Westerners [1712].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Famous Western., 1947 (Box 96)
  - Latin Quarter [1984].; sw: Marcel Klauber; series: Deluxe., 1954 (Box 68, 78)
  - Laughing Irish Eyes [3522]., 1936. (Box 98)
  - The Lawless Eighties [1903].; sw: Kenneth Ganet., 1956 (Box 108)
  - Law of the Golden West [1687].; sw: Norman S. Hall; series: All Star., 1949 (Box 78)
  - Lay That Rifle Down [6036].; sw: Barry Shipman; series: Peerless., 1954 (Box 131)
  - Leadville Gunslinger [1875].; sw: M. Coates Webster; series: Famous Western., 1951 (Box 115)
  - The Leavenworth Case [3526].; sw: Albert DeMond, Sidney Sutherland., 1936 (Box 96, 98)
  - Lightnin' In the Forest [1648].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Variety., 1947 (Box 121)
  - Lightnin' Strikes Twice [1583].; sw: Royal Cole; series: Variety., 1946 (Box 110)
  - Lights of Old Santa Fe [1326].; sw: Gordon Kahn, Bob Williams., 1944 (Box 111)
  - London Blackout Murders [1172]., 1942. (Box 91)
  - Lone Star Raiders [915].; series: Mesquiteer., 1940 (Box 73)
  - The Lone Texas Ranger [1417].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Red Ryder Western., 1944 (Box 111)
  - Lonely Heart Bandits [1792].; sw: Gene Lewis; series: Variety., 1950 (Box 65)
  - Lonely Hearts Club; [1561].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Victory., 1945 (Box 106)
  - Love Ahoy [643?]. (Box 77)
  - Love,Honor, and Goodbye [1479].; sw: Arthur Phillips, Lee Loeb; series: Super Deluxe., 1945 (Box 103)
  - Love is a Fable [?].; sw: Edmund Seward., 1937 (Box 127)
  - Madonna of the Desert [1541].; sw: Albert DeMond; series: Variety., 1947 (Box 122)
  - The Madonna's Secret [1558].; sw: Bradbury Foote, William Thiele; series: Victory., 1945 (Box 103)
  - Magic Fire [1980].; sw: Bertita Harding, E.A. Dupont, David Chantler., 1954 (Box 85, 124, 130)
  - The Magnificent Rogue [1577].; sw: Dane Lussier; series: Anniversary., 1946 (Box 100)
  - The Main Street Kid [1478].; sw: Jerry Sackheim, John K. Butler; series: Variety., 1947 (Box 106)
  - A Man Betrayed [1043]., 1940. (Box 136)
  - Man from Cheyenne [1123].; series: Roy Rogers., 1941 (Box 67)
  - The Man from Frisco [1091]., 1943. (Box 85)
  - Man from Music Mountain [709].; series: Autry., 1938 (Box 68)
  - The Man from Oklahoma [1328].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Premiere., 1945 (Box 81)
  - Man from Texas [1909].; sw: Horace McCoy and Allen Rivkin; series: Deluxe., 1954 (Box 108)
  - Man of Conguest [734], 1939. (Box 86)
  - Manhattan Merry-Go-Round [663].; sw: Harry Sauber., 1937 (Box 89)
  - Mantrap [1179]., 1943. (Box 92)
  - Marshal of Amarillo [1717].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Famous Western., 1948 (Box 78)
  - Marshal of Cripple Creek [1617].; sw: Earle Snell; series: Red Ryder., 1946 (Box 137)
  - Marshal of Laredo [1510].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Red Ryder Western., 1945 (Box 88)
  - Marshall of Reno [1411]., 1944. (Box 111)
  - Mavourneen [772], 1937. (Box 126)
  - Meet the Missus [1039]., 1940. (Box 132)
  - Melody and Moon Light [1044]., 1940. (Box 133)
  - Melody Ranch [1005]., 1940. (Box 90, 120)
  - Mercy Island [1077]., 1941. (Box 63)
  - Mexicana [1473].; sw: Frank Gill, Jr.; series: Super Deluxe., 1945 (Box 103)
  - Minnesota [1474].; sw: Norman Reilly Raine; series: Deluxe., 1951 (Box 110)
  - Missing Men [?]., n.d. (Box 89)
  - Missing Women [1906].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Variety., 1950 (Box 107)
  - The Missourians [1851].; sw: Thames Williamson., 1948 (Box 79, 98)
  - Mr. District Attorney [1155]., 1942. (Box 98)
  - Mr. District Attorney in the Carter Case [1060]., 1941. (Box 64, 119)
  - Mojave Firebrand [1309]., 1943. (Box 100)
  - Moonlight Masquerade [1151]., 1942. (Box 98)
  - Moonrise [1747].; sw: Charles Haas; series: Deluxe., 1947 (Box 81)
  - The Morgue is Always Open [1192]., 1943. (Box 115)
  - Mountain Moon Light [1061]., 1941 (Box 78)
  - Mountain Rhythm [806].; series: Autry., 1939 (Box 128)
  - Mountain Rhythm [1158].; series: Anniversary., 1942 (Box 92)
  - Murder in the Music Hall [1545].; sw: Frances Hyland, Laszlo Gorog; series: Deluxe., 1945 (Box 137)
  - My Best Gal [1242]., 1943. (Box 112)
  - My Buddy [1273].; sw: Arnold Manoff., 1944 (Box 68, 118)
  - My Pal Trigger [1427].; sw: Jack Townle y, John K. Butler; series: Special., 1946 (Box 68)
  - My Sister's Destiny [1760]., 1949. (Box 66)
  - My Wife's Relatives [866]., 1938. (Box 74)
  - Mysterious Miss X [860]., 1938. (Box 74)
  - The Mysterious Mr. Valentine [1548].; sw: M.M. Rai son; series: Jubilee., 1946 (Box 137)
  - Mystery Broadcast [1234]., 1943. (Box 116)
  - Navajo Trail Raiders [1723].; sw: M. Coates Webster; series: Famous Western., 1949 (Box 78)
  - Navy Blues [639]., 1937. (Box 105)
  - Nevada City [1026]., 1941. (Box 133)
  - New Faces [1447].; sw: Stanle y Paley, June Carroll; series: Anniversary., 1944 (Box 106)
  - New Frontior [818].; series: Mesquiteer., 1939 (Box 127)
  - The Night Hawk [858]., 1938. (Box 74)
  - Night Riders of Montana [1853].; sw: M. Coates Webster; series: Famous Western., 1950 (Box 98)
  - Night Time in Nevada [1624].; sw: Sloan Nibely; series: Premiere-Trucolor., 1948 (Box 123)
  - Night Train to Memphis [1540].; sw: Dorrell McGowen and Stuart E. McGowan; series: Anniversary., 1945 (Box 122)
  - Nobody's Darling [1187]., 1943. (Box 116)
  - North of the Great Divide [1836].; sw: Eric Taylor; series: Premiere Trucolor., 1950 (Box 109)
  - O, My Darling Clementine [1235]., 1943. (Box 116)
  - Oh, Susanna [601]., 1936. (Box 76)
  - Oklahoma Annie [6031].; sw: Jack Henley and Charles E. Roberts; series: Judy Canova Special., 1951 (Box 131)
  - Oklahoma Outlaws [1012], 1940. (Box 75)
  - The Old Barn Dance [707], 1937. (Box 96)
  - The Old Corral [603].; sw: Sherman Lowe, Joseph Poland., 1936 (Box 76)
  - The Old Frontier [1694].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Action Western., 1950 (Box 119)
  - The Old Homestead [1145]., 1942. (Box 97)
  - Old Los Angeles [1654].; sw: Gerald Adams; series: Deluxe., 1947 (Box 121)
  - Old Oklahoma Plains [1812].; sw: Arthur Orloff., 1951 (Box 107)
  - Old Oklahoma Plains [1814].; sw: M.M. Raison; series: Paramount., 1952 (Box 111)
  - An Old Spanish Custom [1922]., 1951 (Box 84, 108)
  - On the Old Spanish Trail [1527].; sw: A. Sloan Nibley; series: Premiere Trucolor., 1947 (Box 123)
  - One Exciting Week [1446].; sw: Jack Townley; series: Victory., 1945 (Box 101)
  - One For the Road [1953].; sw: Irving Shulman; series: Deluxe., 1952 (Box 95)
  - Oregon Trail Scouts [1615].; sw: Earle Snell; series: Red Ryder., 1946 (Box 136)
  - Orphans of the Street [787]., 1938. (Box 128)
  - Out California Way [1587].; sw: Betty Burbridge; series: All Star Western., 1946 (Box 121)
  - The Outcast [1969].; sw: Warren Duff; series: Deluxe., 1953 (Box 130)
  - Outlaws of Santa Fe [S31].; sw: Norman S. Hall., 1943 (Box 131)
  - Outlaws of Sonora [716].; series: Mesquiteers., 1938 (Box ?)
  - Outcasts of the Trail [1688].; sw: Olive Cooper; series: Action Western., 1949 (Box 117)
  - Outlaws of Sioux City [1616].; sw: Earl Snell; series: Red Ryder., 1946 (Box 137)
  - Outlaws of the Great Divide [193?].; series: Mesquiteers., n.d. (Box 79)
  - Overland Trail Riders [1815].; sw: M.M. Raison; series: Paramount Rex Allen., 1952 (Box 119)
  - Pals of the Golden West [1840].; sw: Eric Taylor, Albert DeMond; series: Premiere., 1951 (Box 93)
  - Pals of the Pecos [1013].; series: Mesquiteers., 1941 (Box 135)
  - Papa Married a Morman [2027].; sw: Warren Duff; series: Deluxe., 1956 (Box 81)
  - Paradise Express [675]., 1937. (Box 71)
  - Pardon My Stripes [1070]., 1941. (Box 117)
  - Paradise Park [662]., n.d. (Box 104)
  - Pardon My Toehold [1767].; sw: Albert DeMond; series: Variety., 1949 (Box 102)
  - Passkey to Danger [1550].; sw: William Hagens; series: Jubilee., 1945 (Box 137)
  - A Perilous Voyage [1918].; sw: Richard Wormser; series: Deluxe., 1952 (Box 84)
  - Petticoat Politics [1056]., 1940. (Box 132)
  - Phantom of the Race Tracks [1801].; sw: Ronald Davidson., 1955 (Box 65)
  - Phantom Plainsmen [1119].; series: Mesquiteer., 1942 (Box 65)
  - The Phantom Speaks [1463].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Anniversary., 1944 (Box 109)
  - The Pilgrim Lady [1542].; sw: Dane Lussier; series: Anniversary., 1945 (Box 137)
  - Pioneer Marshal [1692].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Action Western., 1949 (Box 88)
  - Pioneers of the West [911].; series: Mesquiteer., 1940 (Box 79)
  - Pirate Submarine [1768?].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Variety., 1950 (Box 66)
  - Pistol Packin' Mama [1248]., 1943. (Box 111)
  - The Pittsburg Kid [1057]., 1941. (Box 85)
  - Plainsman and the Lady [1470].; sw: Richard Wormser; series: Deluxe., 1946 (Box 110)
  - The Plundorers [1753].; sw: James Edward Grant; series: Deluxe., 1948 (Box 65)
  - Portia on Trial [642]., 1937. (Box 77)
  - Port of Forty Thieves [1258]., 1944. (Box 117)
  - Post Office Investigator [1771].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Variety., 1949 (Box 65)
  - Powder River Rustlers [1726].; sw: Richard Wormser; series: Famous Western., 1949 (Box 17)
  - Prairie Moon [705]., 1938. (Box 86)
  - Prairie Pioneers [1017]., 1940. (Box 99)
  - The Presidents Mystery [634]., 1936. (Box 90)
  - Pride of Maryland [1780].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Variety., 1950 (Box 103)
  - Pride of the Navy [859].; series: Showman Group., 1938 (Box 77)
  - Pride of the Plains [1403].; sw: Robert Williams., 1943 (Box 118)
  - Prince of the Plains [1685].; sw: Louise Rousseau, Albert DeMond; series: All-Star., 1948 (Box 71)
  - Prison Nurse [751]., 1937. (Box 80)
  - Prisoners in Petticoats [1787].; sw: Bradbury Foote; series: Variety., 1950 (Box 102)
  - Public Enemies [1067]., 1941. (Box 64, 78)
  - Puddin' Head [1031]., 1941. (Box 136)
  - Prodigal's Mother [1177].; sw: Frances Hyland., 1943 (Box 115)
  - Rags to Riches [1078]., 1941. (Box 62, 78)
  - Raiders of Sunset Pass [1402]., 1943. (Box 118)
  - Raiders of the Range [1115].; series: Mesquiteer., 1942 (Box 66)
  - Rainbow Over Texas [1428].; sw: Gerald Geraghty; series: Rogers premiere., 1945 (Box 77, 124)
  - Ranger and the Lady [927]., 1940. (Box 113)
  - Ranger of Cherokee Strip [1690].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Action Western., 1949 (Box 632)
  - Rebel Island [1971].; sw: Bruce Manning; series: Deluxe., 1954 (Box 69, 84)
  - Red Horizon [1942].; sw: Richard Wormser; series: Deluxe., 1953 (Box 87)
  - Red Menace [1757].; sw: Albert DeMond, Gerald Geraghty; series: Special., 1948 (Box 109)
  - Red River Range [817].; series: Mesquiteers., 1938 (Box 128)
  - Red River Renegades [1530].; sw: Norman S. Hall; series: Superior., 1946 (Box 122)
  - Red River Shore [1817].; sw: Arthur Orloff; series: Paramount., 1953 (Box 119)
  - Red River Valley [3570]., 1936. (Box 114)
  - Redwood Forest Trail [1801].; sw: Bradford Ropes; series: Paramount., 1949 (Box 83, 109)
  - The Reluctant Bachelor [720?]., n.d. (Box 82)
  - Remember Pearl Harbor [1140]., 1942. (Box 93)
  - Rendezvous with Annie [1578].; sw: Mary Loos, Richard Sale; series: Deluxe., 1946 (Box 110)
  - Renegades of Sonora [1719].; sw: M. Coates Webster; series: Famous Western., 1948 (Box 72)
  - Return at Dawn [1465].; sw: Richard Weil; series: Anniversary., 1944 (Box 109)
  - Return of Casanova [1236]., 1943. (Box 116)
  - Rhythm in the Clouds [654]., 1937. (Box 72)
  - Ride Tenderfoot Ride [907].; series: Autry., 1940 (Box 77)
  - Ride the Man Down [1928].; sw: Mary C. McCall Jr.; series: Deluxe., 1951 (Box 114, 138)
  - Riders of the Black Hills [717]., 1938. (Box 80, 88)
  - Riders of the Range [1115]., 1942. (Box 66)
  - Riders of the Rio Grande [1216]., 1943. (Box 114)
  - Ridin' Down the Canyon [1221]., 1942. (Box 116)
  - Ridin' a Rainbow [1001]., 1940. (Box 120)
  - Rio Grande Raiders [1537 or 1634].; sw: Norton S. Parker; series: Superior., 1946 (Box 122, 135)
  - Road to Alcatraz [1476].; sw: Dwight Babcock; Jerry Sackheim; series: Jubilee., 1944 (Box 103)
  - Robin Hood of Texas [1604].; sw: John K. Butler; Earle Snell; series: Sup. Deluxe., 1947 (Box 135)
  - Robin Hood of the Pecos [1023]., 1940. (Box 135)
  - Rock Island Trail [1775].; sw: James Edward Grant; series: Deluxe., 1949 (Box 102)
  - Rodeo King and the Señorita [1808].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Paramount., 1951 (Box 109)
  - Romance on the Run [650]., 1938. (Box 76)
  - Rookies on Parade [1040]., 1941. (Box 132)
  - Rose of the Yukon [1756].; sw: Norman S. Hall; series: Variety., 1948 (Box 107)
  - Rosie the Riveter [1232]., 1943. (Box 115)
  - Rosita from Rio [1941].; sw: Arthur T. Horman; series: Estelita Special., 1952 (Box 87)
  - Rough Riders of Cheyenne [1533].; sw: Elizabeth Beecher; series: Superior., 1945 (Box 122)
  - Rough Riders of Durango [1734].; sw: M. Coates Webster; series: Famous Western., 1950 (Box 119)
  - Round Up Time in Texas [602]., 1937. (Box 72, 76)
  - Rovin' Tumbleweeds [904].; series: Autry., 1939 (Box 90)
  - The Ruby and the Pearl [1966].; sw: Dale Eunson, Katherine Albert; series: Deluxe., 1953 (Box 95)
  - Rustlers on Horseback [1733].; sw: Richard Wormser; series: Famous Western., 1950 (Box 81)
  - Saddle Pals [1606].; sw: Olive Cooper, Bob Williams, Jerry Sackheim; series: Sup. Deluxe., 1947 (Box 136)
  - Saga of Death Valley [922].; series: Roy Rogers., 1939 (Box 75, 105)
  - Salt Lake Raiders [1729].; s w: M. Coates Webster; series: Famous Western., 1950 (Box 117)
  - San Antone Ambush [1691].; sw: Norman S. Hall; series: Action Western., 1949 (Box 119)
  - San Antonio Kid [1412]., 1944. (Box 104)
  - San Fernando Valley [1325].; sw: Dorrell and Stuart McGowan., 1944 (Box 104)
  - Santa Fe Passage [1949].; sw: Lillie Hayward; series; Deluxe., 1952 (Box 129)
  - Santa Fe Saddlemates [1434].; sw: Bennett Cohen., 1945 (Box 104)
  - Santa Fe Scouts [1214].; series: Mesquiteers., 1943 (Box 116)
  - Santa Fe Stampede [815].; series: Mesquiteer., 1938 (Box 97, 128)
  - Sante Fe Uprising [1612].; sw: Earle Snell; series: Red Ryder., 1946 (Box 135)
  - Scatterbrain [989]., 1940. (Box 110)
  - Scotland Yard Investigation [1482].; sw: Randall Faye; series: Anniversary., 1945 (Box 107)
  - Sea Hornet [1661].; sw: Gerald D. Adams; series: Deluxe., 1951 (Box 123)
  - Sea of Lost Ships [1926].; sw: Richard Collins, Norman R. Raine; series: Deluxe., 1952 (Box 93, 134)
  - Secret Service Investigator [1745].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Variety., 1948 (Box 81)
  - Secrets of Monte Carlo [1797].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Variety., 1951 (Box 65)
  - Secrets of Scotland Yard [1265]., 1944. (Box 62)
  - Shadows of Tombstone [1818].; sw: Gerald Geraghty., 1953 (Box 108)
  - Shadows on the Sage [1211].; series: Mesquiteers., 1942 (Box 115)
  - The Shanghai Story [1968].; sw: Seton I. Miller, Steve Fisher; series: Deluxe., 1953 (Box 68, 129)
  - The Sheik Steps Out [560]., 1937. (Box 79)
  - She Married a Cop [841]., 1939. (Box 74)
  - Shepherd of the Ozarks [1135]., 1942. (Box 65)
  - Sheriff of Cimarron [1433].; sw: Bennett Cohen; series: Superior Western., 1944 (Box 111)
  - Sheriff of Las Vegas [1416].; sw: Norman S. Hall., 1944 (Box 106, 125)
  - Sheriff of Redwood Valley [1516].; sw: Earle Snell; series: Red Ryder Western., 1945 (Box 66)
  - Sheriff of Sun-Down [A-403].; sw: Norman W. Hall., 1944 (Box 129)
  - Sheriff of Tombstone [1025]., 1941. (Box 135)
  - Sheriff of Wichita [1720].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Famous Western., 1948 (Box 64)
  - Shine on Texas Moon [1523].; sw: Paul Gangelin, Mauri Grashin; series: Roy Rogers Premiere., 1946 (Box 103)
  - Shot in the Dark [1982].; sw: Frederic Louis Fox, John K. Butler., 1955 (Box 84)
  - Sierra Sue [1103]., 1941. (Box 91)
  - Silent Partner [1239]., 1943. (Box 120)
  - Silver City Bonanza [1804].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Paramount., 1950 (Box 108)
  - Silver Rock [1972]., 1953. (Box 68)
  - Sing, Dance, Plenty Hot [994]., 1940. (Box 110)
  - Sing, Neighbor, Sing [1266]., 1944. (Box 118)
  - Singing Guns [1030].; sw: Dorrell and Stuart McGowan., 1949 (Box 136)
  - Singing Hills [1004]., 1941. (Box 112)
  - Singing Kid from Pine Ridge [608]., n.d. (Box 104)
  - Sioux City Sue [1603].; sw: Olive Cooper; series: Supreme Deluxe., 1946 (Box 137)
  - Sis Hopkins [1055]., 1941. (Box 132)
  - Sitting on the Moon [3528]., 1936. (Box 98)
  - Sleepy Lagoon [1190]., 1943. (Box 92)
  - Sleepy-Time Gal [1088]., 1941. (Box 89)
  - Slippy McGee [1641].; sw: Norman S. Hall & Jerry Gruskin; series: Variety., 1947 (Box 122)
  - Son of God's Country [1683].; sw: Paul Gangelin, Earle Snell; series: All Star., 1948 (Box 63)
  - Song of Arizona [1422].; sw: Bradford Ropes; series: Roy Rogers-Premiere., 1945 (Box 68, 112, 124)
  - Song of Nevada [1323]., 1944. (Box 104)
  - Song of Texas [1223].; sw: John K. Butler., 1942 (Box 77)
  - Song of Youth [1929].; sw: Alan LeMay; series: Deluxe., 1951 (Box 83, 134)
  - Sons of the Pioneers [1127].; series: Roy Rogers., 1942 (Box 69, 91)
  - S.O.S. Tidal Wave [747]., 1939. (Box 80)
  - South of Caliente [1849].; sw: Eric Taylor; series: Premiere., 1950 (Box 93)
  - South of Rio [1689].; sw: Norman S. Hall; series: Action Western., 1949 (Box 71)
  - South of San Antone [1940].; sw: Steve Fisher; series: Deluxe., 1952 (Box 114)
  - South of Santa Fe [1124]., 1941. (Box 91)
  - South of the Border [901].; series: Autry., 1939 (Box 73)
  - Southward Ho [R 6]., 1939. (Box 131)
  - Specter of the Rose [1566].; sw: Ben Hecht., 1945 (Box 100)
  - Spoilers of the Forest [1959].; sw: Bruce Manning., 1956 (Box 123, 129)
  - Spoilers of the North [1642].; sw: Milton S. Raison; series: Variety., 1946 (Box 122)
  - Spoilers of the Plains [1838].; sw: Sloan Nibley; series: Premiere., 1950 (Box 93)
  - Springtime in the Sierras [1529].; sw: Sloan Nibley; series: Premiere Trucolor., 1946 (Box 121)
  - Stagecoach to Denver [1613].; sw: Earle Snell; series: Red Ryder., 1946 (Box 135)
  - Stand Up and Sing [883].; sw: Doris Malloy., 1939 (Box 70)
  - Stardust on the Trail [1201]., 1942. (Box 116)
  - State Highway Patrol [884].; sw: Earl Snell and Gordon Kahn; series: Showmen's Group., 1939 (Box 105)
  - State Police Patrol [1781].; sw: Albert DeMond; series: Variety., 1950 (Box 101)
  - Storm over Bengal [728]., 1938. (Box 82)
  - Strangers in the Night [1444]., 1944. (Box 106)
  - Street of Missing Men [842]., 1939. (Box 74, 79)
  - Streets of San Francisco [1763].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Variety., 1949 (Box 101)
  - Sundown in Santa Fe [1684].; sw: Norman S. Hall; series: All Star., 1948 (Box 64)
  - Sundown Kid [S 21]., 1942. (Box 131)
  - Sunset in El Dorado [1421].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Rogers premiere., 1945 (Box 84)
  - Sunset in the West [1832].; sw: Gerald Geraghty; series: Premiere Trucolor., 1950 (Box 109)
  - Sunset in Wyoming [1102]., 1941. (Box 91)
  - Sunset on the Trail [1125]., 1942. (Box 91)
  - Sunset Serenade [1128].; series: Roy Rogers., 1942 (Box 69)
  - The Sun Shines Bright [1952].; sw: Laurence Stallings; series: Deluxe. (Box 95, 129)
  - Sun Valley Cyclone [1517].; sw: Earle Snell; series: Red Ryder Western., 1945 (Box 102)
  - Surrender [1760].; sw: James Edward Grant; series: Deluxe., 1949 (Box 66)
  - Susanna Pass [1627].; sw: Sloan Nibley, John K. Butler; series: Premiere Trucolor., 1948 (Box 110)
  - Swift Lightning [648].; sw: Jack Townley., 1938 (Box 76)
  - Swingin' on a Rainbow [1452].; sw: Olive Cooper, John Gray; series: Anniversary., 1944 (Box 113)
  - Tabarin [1925].; sw: Hooston Branch., 1951 (Box 96, 138)
  - Tahiti Honey [1173]., 1942. (Box 91)
  - Tarnished [1565].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Variety., 1949 (Box 102)
  - Tell it to a Star [1254].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Anniversary., 1944 (Box 66, 117)
  - Ten Nights in a Barroom [1079]., 1941. (Box 120)
  - Tenth Avenue Kid [729]., 1938. (Box 88)
  - The Texas Legionnaires [1962].; sw: Warren Duff; series: Deluxe., 1955 (Box 97, 129)
  - That Brennen Girl [1154].; sw: Doris Anderson; series: Deluxe., 1946 (Box 136)
  - That's My Gal [1487].; sw: Joseph Hoffman; series: Major Truodor., 1946 (Box 72)
  - That's My Man [1580].; sw: Steve Fisher; Bradley King., 1946 (Box 106)
  - That Towsend Girl [1914].; sw: Lawrence Kimble; series: Deluxe., 1951 (Box 83)
  - Then You'll Remember Me [1947].; sw: Houston Branch; series: Deluxe., 1952 (Box 94, 97)
  - Thoroughbreds [1458].; sw: Wellyn Totman., 1944 (Box 100)
  - Thou Shalt Not Kill [978]., 1939. (Box 113)
  - Three Little Sisters [1259]., 1944. (Box 123)
  - The Thrill Man [1743].; sw: Franklin Andreon, Sol Shor; series: Variety., 1948 (Box 63)
  - Thumbs Up [1149]., 1943. (Box 98)
  - Thunder in God's Country [1805].; sw: Arthur E. Orloff; series: Paramount., 1950 (Box 113)
  - Thundering Caravans [1876].; sw: M. Coates Webster; series: Famous Western., 1952 (Box 115)
  - Ticket to Paradise [3553]., 1936. (Box 114)
  - The Tiger Woman [1488].; sw: George Carleton Brown; series: Jubilee., 1945 (Box 74)
  - Timberjack [1974].; sw: Allen Rivkin; series: Deluxe., 1954 (Box 68, 84, 130)
  - Timber Trail [1681].; sw: Bob Williams; series: All Star., 1947 (Box 81)
  - Too Late for Tears [1010].; sw: Roy Huggins., 1948 (Box 73)
  - The Topeka Terror [A404].; sw: Norman S. Hall., 1944 (Box 131)
  - The Toughest Man In Tombstone [1943].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Deluxe., 1951 (Box 67, 93)
  - Traffic in Crime [1469].; sw: David Lang; series: Jubilee., 1946 (Box 101)
  - Trail Blazers [1011]., 1940. (Box 75)
  - Trail of Kit Carson [A 406].; sw: Jack Netteford and Albert DeMond; series: Action Western., 1945 (Box 131)
  - Trail of Robinhood [1835].; sw: Gerald Geraghty; series: Premiere Trucolor., 1950 (Box 109)
  - Trail to San Antone [1601].; sw: Jack Nattaford, Luci Ward, Olive Cooper; series: Autry., 1946 (Box 109)
  - Treasure Hunt [657]., n.d. (Box 70)
  - The Trespasser [1568].; sw: Jerry Gruskin, Darrell and Stuart E. McGowan; series: Variety., 1947 (Box 107)
  - Trigger, Jr. [1834].; sw: Gerald Geraghty; series: Premiere Trucolor., 1949 (Box 109)
  - Tropical Heat Wave [1941].; sw: Arthur T. Horman; series: Estelita Special., 1952 (Box 87, 115)
  - Trouble for Two [776]., n.d. (Box 129)
  - The Tueson Raiders [1410]., 1944. (Box 120)
  - Tuxedo Junction [1074]., 1941. (Box 77)
  - Twilight in the Sierras [1831].; sw: Sloan Nibley; series: Premiere Trucolor., 1949 (Box 111)